crunchgear.com 2017-12-28

# AOL Privacy

Oath, part of the Verizon family of companies, consists of over 50 digital and mobile [brands](http://oath.com/our-brands/) globally, including HuffPost, Yahoo News, Yahoo Sports, Tumblr, and AOL, as well as advertising platforms such as ONE by AOL, BrightRoll, and Gemini.

Below are highlights of the full [Oath Privacy Policy](http://privacy.aol.com/privacy-policy/), which applies to the collection and use of information from any device used to access or connect to Oath branded or affiliated websites, services, or software that link to this Privacy Policy. Para leer este documento en español haz clic [aquí](http://privacy.aol.com/privacidad/).

Similarly, the [Yahoo Privacy Policy](https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/index.htm) will apply on Yahoo branded sites and affiliated products, services, and technologies that link to the Yahoo Privacy Policy. If there is a conflict between the Oath Privacy Policy and the Verizon or Yahoo privacy policies, the Oath Privacy Policy will apply when you are on an Oath product, service, or brand site that links to this policy and the Yahoo Privacy Policy will apply on Yahoo branded product, service, technology, or sites that link to the Yahoo policy. Additional privacy information is available in the [Verizon Privacy Policy](http://www.verizon.com/about/privacy/).

### What's New

  * The [Oath Privacy Policy](http://privacy.aol.com/privacy-policy) was updated effective June 13, 2017.
  * The AOL company name has changed to Oath. The way we handle your information hasn't changed, so the Oath Privacy Policy will continue to govern when you are on previously branded AOL products, services, or technologies, including AOL Mail, AOL.com, HuffPost, Engadget, TechCrunch, Moviefone, and Makers.

### How to Opt-Out

You can opt-out of interest-based advertising delivered by the ONE by AOL advertising services. See [Your Choices](http://privacy.aol.com/advertising-and-privacy/).

### Information We Collect and Receive

We collect and receive information about you and your device when you give it to us directly, when you use our services across your devices, and from certain third-party sources.

### Internet Advertising

Our ability to provide free content and services depends on advertising. Some of our ads are displayed based on the page visited, but many of our ads are targeted to you based on your interests and other information we have about you. [Learn more](http://privacy.aol.com/advertising-and-privacy/) about how internet advertising works and your choices.

### Your Choices

  * You can opt out of receiving interest-based ads from us when you browse the web by visiting the [Digital Advertising Alliance's consumer choice page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) and selecting "AOL Advertising," "BrightRoll," and "Yahoo Inc." If you are a Yahoo registered user, you also must opt out of ads on [Yahoo](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/opt_out/targeting).
  * You may control how certain information from your mobile device, including your location, may be collected and used through your device and mobile application permissions.
  * AOL services offer [Marketing Preferences](http://marketingpreferences.aol.com/) to control how we communicate offers to AOL registered users.
  * You can control the collection and use of AOL [Search information](http://search.aol.com/aol/settings).
  * AOL registered users can manage their accounts at [My Account](http://myaccount.aol.com/).
  * You can manage some technologies using [browser controls](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers#cookies).
  * Individual products or services may offer additional controls or preferences.

### Information Sharing

Oath may share your information in limited circumstances, including when we have your consent to do so or when sharing is necessary to protect Oath or comply with the law. Our agents and contractors may have access to your information, but only to perform services for Oath. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. We may, however, share [non-personally identifiable information](http://privacy.aol.com/definitions) with select business partners.

### How we use your Information

The information we collect and receive is used to provide our Services, to improve our Services, and to offer effective advertising, which helps us keep most of our Services free.

### How to Contact Us

**Oath Privacy**  
22000 AOL Way  
Dulles, VA 20166  
privacyquestions@aol.com
